

# GENÍS GILAVERT BERLANA

Diluvi nº 7, 2º 2ª, Barcelona 08012

**4** 93 448 36 23 **609 156 909** 

■ anonymousheimer@gmail.com

# **SUMMARY**

Leadership skills, analytic capacity and excellent problem solving skills.

Big potential in mathematics and programming.

Two years in the mathematics degree with mention in computing.

At change of job to computer systems administrator, stopped the carreer and continued expanding knowledge with others programming languages.

Currently, working and studying several courses of Programming and English.

| EMPLOYMENT HISTORY  |                                |
|---|--------------------------------|
| Waiter<br>Bar Oasis - Hospitalet de Llobregat   | January 1997 to January 1999   |
| Football referee<br>Federació Catalana de Futbol - Barcelona  | January 1998 to January 2004   |
| Bellboy<br>Grupo de Hoteles Gargallo - Barcelona  | March 2002 to June 2002        |
| Collaborator<br>Jornadas Internacionales de fisioterapia - Barcelona  | October 2004 to October 2004   |
| Commercial Publingenios - Barcelona   | November 2004 to January 2005  |
| Administrative Assistant Air France - Tremblay-en-France  | January 2005 to September 2005 |
| Network Operator for telefonica<br>Spark Ibérica - Barcelona  | October 2005 to December 2005  |
| Soldier in the specialty of transmissions<br>Ministerio de Defensa - Madrid   | April 2006 to August 2017      |
| <b>Teacher of programing of Video Games with POO an Espai Barcelona -</b> I was invited to give a class of programing of Video Games with POO and |                                |
| Computer systems administrator<br>Omega Peripherals - Barcelona   | May 2017 to working currently  |
| TRAINING  |                                |
| Federació Catalana de Futbol Camp Barcelona Football referes title: Sports  | 1998                           |

| TRAINING  |      |
|---|------|
| Federació Catalana de Futbol Camp<br>Barcelona<br>Football referee title: Sports                      | 1998 |
| Institut Eduard Fontserè Hospitalet de Llobregat Baccalaureate title: Technological                   | 2003 |
| Dirección General de Tráfico  Barcelona  Driving license class B                                      | 2003 |
| Spark Ibérica Barcelona Network Operator course: Computing  | 2005 |
| Acuartelamiento San Fernando<br>Zaragoza<br>IT Essentials course: PC Hardware and Software: Computing | 2011 |
| CAMPUS 25   | 2011 |

Barcelona

University access certificate

Universitat Pompeu Fabra

Barcelona

Decoding Algebra course: Mathematics

Universitat Autónoma de Barcelona

Barcelona

2013

Course 1 of Design and creation of videogames: Videogames programing

Universitat de Barcelona 2017

Barcelona

# Two years in the mathematics degree with mention in computing: Pure mathematics

- subjects of computing degree:
  - Algorísmica
  - Programació II
  - Estructura de dades
  - Disseny de Software
  - Projecte Integrat de Software

Commvault 2018

New Jersey

Commvault Technical Sales Professional - CVTSP19

Espai 2018

Barcelona

Higher course of development and implementation of web applications

I designer not finished yet ...

Barcelona

**Programing of Video Games with Unreal Engine 4** 

CEPI-BASE not finished yet ...

Barcelona Course of Visual C#/C++.NET and SQL

# KNOWLEDGES, SKILLS AND APTITUDES

# **Programming languages**

C, C++, C#, R, Java, Mathematica, Powershell, Python, PHP and Javascript

# **Others languages**

HTML5, CSS3, jquery, Linux, ajax and SQL

# **Languages**

Native: Spanish, Catalan

Medium: English (level B1, studying for B2

offical exam)

# **Work platforms**

Netbeans AndroidStudio Mathematica Eclipse

Microsoft Visual Studio Visual Studio Code

# **Applications**

Videogame: Bubbles math Javascript

competition of web videogames

**backup analysis** Java

free

Videogame: FlyAway Android

subject "integrated software project"

Multimedia player Java subject "programing II"

# **Programming projects**

Test web PHP

php final exam

Commercial web HTML5 and CSS3

html final exam

Kangaroo service Java

subject "software design"

movies and series service Java

subject "software design"

Other programs C and C++

various subjects

### AWARDS AND ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

# university awards

Qualification of Honor's Registration in the subject "Elements de programació"

#### other awards

Contest of programming a math videogame in Javascript

# individual sports

# **☼** Athletics

- 1º Classified T cross of "Hospitalet de Llobregat"
- 1º Classified Trophy "ROBERTO CABREJAS" in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE" (3 km) Obtaining the record of the lower time in the institute`s history
- 1º Classified T Militar trophy "Trofeo SAN FERNANDO" (5 km) in the army

Between the position 100 and 200 of 60 thousand participants in the race of "El Corte inglés" (about 12,5 km in 41 minutes)

#### ir Chess

- 1º Classified T tournament in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"
- 1º Classified T League in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"
- 1º Classified T summer tournament in a English school camp

# Shot with long weapon

1º Classified T Militar trophy "SAN FERNANDO" in the army

# **W** Videogames

1º Classified 2 2 times at tournament of "Super Smash Bros"

# collective sports

# Football

- 1º Classified **Y** Many trophies of league "LAS PLANAS"
- 1º Classified T Champions league "LAS PLANAS"
- 10 Classified T summer tournament played in zone Pedralbes in barcelona

# **Volleyball**

1º Classified T tournament in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"

# **☞** Videogames

Diamond level playing "League of Legends"

In the 10 best players of the world with the champion Heimerdinger in "League of Legends"

1º Classified T tournament of couples playing at "Pro Evolution Soccer"